(
"ai_sub_version": "3.5.1",
"generated_at": "2026-07-28T17:26:47.550709",
"lyrics_prompt_version": 9,
"subtitles_prompt_version": 18,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"any_pending": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": null,
"model_subtitles": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash-lite",
"model_lyrics": "google-gla:gemini-3.1-flash-lite",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true,
"max_storage_gb": 18.0
),
"search": (
"qps": 0.3,
"max_length": 4096,
"web_search_tool": "langsearch",
"timeout": 60.0,
"retries": 3,
"min_wait_seconds": 1.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 10.0,
"multiplier": 2.0
),
"validation_buffer_ms": 2000,
"verification_gap_seconds": 60,
"gap_verification_retries": 1,
"gap_verification_ignore_start": true,
"gap_verification_ignore_end": true
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": false,
"fps": 1.0,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"threshold_mb": 20,
"duration_tolerance_ms": 100,
"encoder": null
),
"start_offset_min": 0
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"lyrics": 4,
"subtitles": 4
),
"retry": (
"per_run": 5,
"max_runs": 3,
"multiplier": 2.0,
"min_wait_seconds": 30.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 300
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": true,
"scrub": false,
"progress_bars": true,
"progress_bar_width": 80,
"progress_bar_refresh_seconds": 1.0
)
Tokoyami Towa 6th Anniversary LIVE
常闇トワ 6周年記念 Rock Festa!!!
Tokoyami Towa 6th Anniversary LIVE - Rock Festa!!!
常闇トワ
Tokoyami Towa
鷹嶺ルイ
Takane Lui
輪堂千速
Rindo Chihaya
IRyS
音乃瀬奏
Otonose Kanade
AZKi
夏色まつり
Natsuiro Matsuri
森カリオペ
Mori Calliope
猫汰つな
Nekota Tsuna
ああ 呆れだす そばに 差し替えられた
Ah, swapped out right beside my exasperation,
現存にかかった 固定解像と
with a fixed resolution hanging over existence.
反則じみた応えじゃ 見透かされてしまうな
Answers that feel like fouls will easily be seen right through.
この道を渡りきっても まだ視界は濁っている
Even if I cross all the way down this road, my vision is still murky.
履き替えた大人になってから 縮みきった歩幅と感情
Since becoming an adult who changed shoes, my stride and emotions have shrunk completely.
削り出した身体に対して 「気付け」と吠えている
Barking at my worn-out body, telling it to "wake up."
はみ出した心じゃ 居られないのならさ
If I can't stay with a heart that overflows,
染み付いたこの青さを 切り離してしまっていい？
is it okay if I just cut away this ingrained naivety?
ずっと語りかけてた日日を 嘆くように
As if lamenting the days I kept talking to,
深い闇に飲み込まれないようにって
praying not to be swallowed by the deep darkness,
決まりきった現実に 応えになんていらない
I don't need any answers for a set-in-stone reality.
逃げ出してしまった。言葉を羽織って
I ran away, cloaked in words,
溶け出した心を胸に隠している
hiding my melting heart inside my chest.
冷え切ってしまった身体を欺くように
As if to deceive my chilled-to-the-bone body,
描きかけたいつかの枯れた夢をなぞっている
I'm tracing the withered dream I once tried to draw.
ああ 暴れだす言葉に 差し替えられた
Ah, swapped out for rampaging words,
幻想にかかった 固定概念と
with fixed stereotypes wrapped in illusion.
止まった理想じゃ 見透かされてしまうな
Stagnant ideals will easily be seen right through.
この道を渡りきっても まだ次回だ 続いていく
Even if I cross all the way down this road, it continues as another time.
履き違えた大人になってから 尖りだした想いの回想
Reminiscing about feelings that grew sharp after becoming a mis-stepped adult.
ずっと見えなくなった足跡 探している
Searching for footsteps that long ago disappeared from view.
はみ出した心じゃ 居られないのならさ
If I can't stay with a heart that overflows,
澄み切ったこの青さを 曝け出してしまっていい？
is it okay if I expose this crystal-clear naivety?
ずっと語りかけてた日日を 隠すように
As if hiding the days I kept talking to,
深い闇に飲み込まれないようにって
praying not to be swallowed by the deep darkness,
決まりきった現実に 答えになんていらない
I don't need any answers for a set-in-stone reality.
逃げ出してしまった 言葉を羽織って
I ran away, cloaked in words,
溶け出した心を 胸に隠している
hiding my melting heart inside my chest.
冷え切ってしまった 身体をだますように
As if to deceive my chilled-to-the-bone body,
描きかけたいつかの枯れた夢を なぞっている
I'm tracing the withered dream I once tried to draw.
ああ 錆び付いている 今をただ不安定に立つ
Ah, standing so precariously in a rusting present.
裏返る脳裏に 汚されてしまった
Defiled in the back of my flipping mind,
あの日の日達に 願っては遡っていた 手放してしまったのに
even though I wished for those days of yore, only to let them go.
逃げ出してしまった 言葉を羽織って
I ran away, cloaked in words,
溶け出した心を 胸に隠している
hiding my melting heart inside my chest.
冷え切ってしまった 身体をだますように
As if to deceive my chilled-to-the-bone body,
描きかけたいつかの 枯れた夢をなぞっている
I'm tracing the withered dream I once tried to draw.
Can you hear me when I cry in desperation?
Nothing comes along with my expectation
How much pain and ache you're feeling? Breathing?
I gotta change this situation
アダルトな着ぐるみ着てる僕
I'm wearing an adult kigurumi suit,
心はいつも不安定天秤シーソー
my heart is always an unstable seesaw balance.
まさかの発言で凍り付く印籠見え隠れ血迷う僕
Unexpected remarks freeze me, my lost self peeking through.
今日の今この瞬間に放とうとする言葉がいつも後ろ髪引く
The words I try to unleash at this very moment always hold me back.
全部ダメダメなんだってしょうじゃもう諦めて
"It's all useless anyway, so just give up!"
鼻からなかったことにしよう!!ラリルラリルラリルラ
Let's just pretend it never happened! Laliraliralira
それじゃダメダメ悪い癖だもうしない!
"If so, that's a bad habit, I won't do it anymore!"
どうせ着せられているならキメキメでいこう!
"Since I'm dressed up anyway, let's look sharp!"
何もかもが暗く黒く見える!
"Everything looks dark and black!"
色メガネ付きのアダルトなパチモンスーツ
An adult knockoff suit with tinted glasses,
必殺技×0で全部消し去ろうか?
shall I erase everything with special moves x 0?
強気な僕(笑)だけど実際は
A bullish me (lol). But in reality,
やっぱり出来映しないの身軽さを奪われ動けない
I still can't pull it off, robbed of my lightness, unable to move.
それでもうまくいこバランスとれてるんだよ!
And yet it's nicely balanced!
きみは耳元でそれを言う!それにしちゃ少し
You whisper that right in my ear! Though compared to that,
あまりじゃないかっていうか不公平じゃない?
isn't it a bit too much? Or rather, isn't it unfair?
どうせ勝ち目なんかないし食い気味でいこう!
There's no chance of winning anyway, so let's dive right in!
i feel this moment no one can take it
そう何回だって伝わらないと意味ない!
"So no matter how many times, it's meaningless unless it gets across!"
今日の今この瞬間が大事なの
"Today's very moment is important!"
奪う権利はあなた方にはない!!
"You don't have the right to take it away!!"
全部ダメダメ!何がダメダメなんでしょう?
"No, no! What's wrong?"
納得いくまで話してよ!どうせ尻尾隠し並べるんだろ
"Talk until you're satisfied! You're just going to make excuses anyway,"
バカみたいとどめを刺す気でいるなら?
"if you intend to deliver the final blow like an idiot?"
納得いくまで話してよ!どうせ屁理屈
"Talk until you're satisfied! If you're just going to line up"
並べるならバカみたいにとどめをさすきでいるなら?
"sophistry and deliver the final blow like an idiot,"
今場所ん中だぞ!
"This is my turf now!"
それでマイペース乱し取れてるんだよ!
"And yet you're disrupting my pace!"
はーい！ということで、え、声はおっぴ、常闇トワ様です！
Haa-i! So, um, the voice is Oppi, Tokoyami Towa-sama!
はい！ということで、なんと、本日6周年を迎えました！
Hai! So, unbelievably, today we reached our 6th anniversary!
イェーイ！ろっ、6！
Yay! Six, six!
悪魔の数字6！
The devil's number 6!
ということは、今年はトワちゃんの歳ということでもいいでしょうか？
That means, can we say this year is Towa-chan's age too?
まあ、良くないか。
Well, maybe not.
いいか！
Good!
まあ、人によってトワちゃんのね、あの歳に浸っていいということで、はい、よろしくお願いします！
Well, depending on the person, you can soak in Towa-chan's age, so yes, nice working with you!
常闇トワ6周年記念ライブでよろしくお願いします！
Welcome to Tokoyami Towa's 6th Anniversary LIVE!
目指せトレンド入り。
Aiming for trending!
そしてね、この後はいろんな告知もありますので、最後まで見ていてくれればなと思います。
And then, there'll be various announcements, so I hope you watch until the end!
はい。
Right!
で、今日なんですけれども、1月3日
Today is January 3rd,
となっておりまして、世間はお休みの日ということで
and since today is a holiday for everyone,
私もお休みの日ということで、本日のライブは前半戦となっております。
I am also on holiday, so today's live is a 2-part event!
よろしくお願いします。
Thank you for your support!
そして、この後はなんとゲストパート！いっぱい、いろんなね、ゲストが出てきてくれるので、楽しんで見ていてくれればなと思います。
And after this, there will be lots of guest parts with various guests appearing, so I hope you enjoy watching!
それでは、
Now then...
ゲストパート、どうぞ！
guest part, please!
闇夜を駆け抜けて 何処へ向かうか
I keep on running through this dark night, I don't know where to go
月明かりだけがただ一つの道標
The moon above is all I see, the only thing in sight that's guiding me
痛みも悲しみも拭い切れず
No matter what, I can't erase it, all of the pain and tears
されどこの胸の炎は消させない
But I won't ever let it win, my spark inside will never dim
誰が為に僕たちは この想いを貫いて
Who were we fighting for all of this time? How do we brave all this pain deep inside?
闇を裂き 陽の下で
Cut through the darkness till you see the light
光さす日まで
Until the day we see it shine
解き放たれた心に宿した火よ
I can feel the fire burning deep inside my heart and my soul
舞い上げ、まとえ 今 夜明けの向こう側へ
I won't let go until we reach the dawn we dreamed to find on this road
君がいる この世界 もう一度愛せるまで
And until the day that we meet again, that I can be right next to you
我が命 果てようとも 繋いで行こう
Oh, even if I lose it all tonight, I won't give up till the end
絆が紡いで 生まれた奇跡を
Together we will make it though, and we will choose our destiny!
喜怒哀楽 夢 揺らめいている現世 互いの正義をまた繰り返し振りかざす
And all the pain, the joy, the suffering that we endure within this life
誰が為に繋ぐ命 交わりもつれる宿命
Who were we living for all of this time? And how did our fates come to be intertwined?
蛇の道 数々の罪 全て薙ぎ払え
Cut through the snakes and the sins that we find, so we can walk this path tonight!
解き放て 今 僕らが起こした火を
Free the fires in your heart, release the passion deep in your soul
舞い上げ 走れば 明日が変わるはず
If we keep on reaching for the sky, I know we'll change tomorrow
君といる この世界 二度と離さずに
And no matter what, I will not let go, I'll stay with you until the end
瞬きを閉じても 想い出すあの日を
Even when I close my eyes today, I remember how I wished and prayed
打ちのめされても 焦がれた未来を
For the future that I longed to see, the dream I fought for endlessly
いつの日か 君に捧げてみせよう
And someday, I will dedicate it all to you, yes, all to you
解き放て 今 僕らが起こした火を
Free the fires in your heart, unleash the spirit burning within
舞い上げ 走れば 明日が変わるはず
Rise up above the pain and tears, and soar towards the dawn today!
君がいた この世界 もう一度愛せるまで
Free the fires in your heart, release the passion deep in your soul
我が命 果てようとも 繋げてゆくよ
If we keep on reaching for the sky, I know we'll change tomorrow
絆が紡いで 生まれた奇跡を
And until the day that we meet again, that I can be right next to you
抱きしめられた記憶から流れ出た赤い雫
From memories of being held so close, red drops flowed out...
人様に見せるものじゃないの
Something never meant for other people's eyes.
伝えなかった言霊がもうひとつの私になって
Unspoken words became another self inside of me,
身体の内側で何かを叫んでる
crying out something deep within my body.
欲しかったのに 悔しかったのに 駄目だよ全部隠しておくの
Though I wanted it so badly, though I regretted it so much, I must hide it all away.
ごめんね
I'm sorry.
悲しいのは一人で十分だからと これ以上醜くなりたいないのと
"Because sadness is enough for just one, and I don't want to become any uglier..."
私の中で誰にも見付けられずにこんな色になるまで泣いていたんだね 綺麗よ
Unseen by anyone inside of me, you cried until you turned this color, didn't you? You are beautiful.
渡しそびれた心から流れ出た青い雫
From the heart I couldn't ever give, blue drops flowed out...
人様に浴びせるものじゃないの
Something never meant to pour on others.
余すところなく飲み込んで遠海の底に沈んで
Swallowing it all down without a trace, sinking to the bottom of a distant sea,
そのまま宝石にでもなれるのを待つわ
I'll wait there, hoping to become a jewel.
ああ
Ah...
本当は嘘で飾って ごくこみたいな暮らしで慰めて
Decorating truth with lies, comforting myself with a fake life,
誰かの悲劇で自分の悲劇を癒して
healing my own tragedy using someone else's pain.
恋しさに溺れた瞬間のままに
Just as I was, the moment I drowned in yearning,
息もできずただ愛してるの
can't even breathe, just "I love you."
悲しいのは一人で十分だからと これ以上醜くなりたいないのと
"Because sadness is enough for just one, and I don't want to become any uglier..."
私の中で誰にも見付けられずにこんな色になるまで泣いていたんだね 綺麗よ
Unseen by anyone inside of me, you cried until you turned this color, didn't you? You are beautiful.
ごめんね
I'm sorry.
ねぇ 綺麗よ
Hey... you are beautiful.
片っ端で丸を作ってしっかり持ってて
Make a circle with one end and hold it tight.
もう片っ端でその丸の後ろをぐるっと回って
With the other end, go around the back of that circle.
間にできたポッケに入って出てくるの待ってて
Go through the pocket formed in between and wait for it to come out.
出てきたところを迎えに来てさあ「せーの」で引っぺいて
Come meet the end where it comes out, and pull it on the count of three.
はじめはなんとも情けない形だとしても 同じだけ力を込めて
Even if at first, it's a bit of a pathetic shape, apply the same amount of strength.
羽は大きく結び目は固く なるようにきつく結んでいて欲しいの
I want you to tie it tight so the wings are big and the knot is firm.
腕はここに思い出は遠くに 置いておいてほしいの
I want you to keep arms here, and memories far away.
羽は大きく結び目は固く なるようにきつく結んでいて欲しいの
I want you to tie it tight so the wings are big and the knot is firm.
欲しいの
I want you to...
手はここに思い出は遠くに 置いて置いて欲しいの 欲しいの
I want dreams here, and memories far away...
片っ端でも引っ張っちゃえば
If you pull on just one end,
ほどけちゃうけど
it will all come undone,
作ったもの壊すのは
but breaking what you've created
はるかに簡単だけど
is far too easy.
だけど解く時も
Even when untying it,
そうちゃんとさ
you should do it properly,
同じようにね
just like before.
せーので引っ張って
Pulling it together on three!
ほぐれやしないようにと願って力を込めては
Wishing it won't fray, I put my strength into it,
広げすぎた羽に
and get bewildered
戸惑う
by these overly spread wings.
羽根は大きく
The wings are big,
結び目は固く
the knot is firm,
なるように気づく結んでいて欲しいの夢はここに
wishing they'd stay tied so our dreams remain right here.
想い出は遠くに
Memories are far away,
日付もそこにあるくらいがいい
and it's nice if the date is right there too.
結ばって引っ張ったりしないでよ
Don't go pulling on our bonds,
浮かごうが帳尻にしないでよ
don't let them float away or balance out!
結んだつもりがほどいてたり
Thinking we tied them, we were undoing them,
緩めたつもりが締めていたり
thinking we loosened them, we were tightening them.
この青くて広い世界に
In this blue and vast world,
無数に散らばった中から
from the countless scattered paths,
別々に二人選んだとを お互いたぐり寄せ合ったんだ
we chose separate ways and pulled them toward each other.
結ばれたんじゃない 結んだんだ
We weren't just bound together; we tied the knot ourselves.
二人でせーので引っ張ったんだ
The two of us pulled together on three!
大きくも小さくもなりすぎないように 力を込めたんだ
Putting in our strength so it wouldn't become too big or too small.
この青くて広い世界に
In this blue and vast world,
無数に散らばった中から
from the countless scattered paths,
別々に二人選んだとを お互いたぐり寄せ合ったんだ
we chose separate ways and pulled them toward each other.
結ばれたんじゃない 結んだんだ
We weren't just bound together; we tied the knot ourselves.
二人でせーので引っ張ったんだ
The two of us pulled together on three!
大きくも小さくもなりすぎないように 力を込めたんだ
Putting in our strength so it wouldn't become too big or too small.
影にそっと隠れるくらいがいいんじゃない？
Isn't it nice to quietly hide in the shadows?
蕾のような花だっていいんじゃない？
Isn't it fine to be a flower like a bud?
秘密にして守るのがいいんじゃない？
Isn't it good to keep it a secret and protect it?
誰にも邪魔されず華麗に咲いてる
Blooming gorgeously without being bothered by anyone.
甘い苦いにハマんなけりゃ
If you don't get hooked on sweet and bitter,
その判断がクダんない
that judgment is pointless.
気に病んで下を向かないでいて
Don't fret and look down.
愛になりちゃいない
You haven't gotten used to love.
無駄に飾らない
Don't decorate needlessly.
綺麗にされた花瓶も
Even a neatly arranged vase
養分も何もいらない
or any fertilizer isn't needed.
その姿が美しい
That appearance is beautiful.
花になって
Become a flower,
ほらニヒルに笑って その顔にぞくぞくして目が離せない
smile mockingly, and I can't take my eyes off that thrilling face.
味見して 君の毒は私の薬って
Taste it: your poison is my medicine,
包んであげるから笑って
I'll wrap you up, so smile.
陰にそっと隠れようがいいんじゃない？
It's okay to quietly hide in the shadows, right?
蕾のような花だっていいんじゃない？
Even if you're a budding flower, isn't that fine?
秘密にして守るのがいいんじゃない？
It's good to keep it a secret and protect it, right?
誰にも邪魔されず華麗に咲いている
Blooming magnificently without anyone bothering you
甘い苦いにはまんない
Not too sweet, not too bitter
その判断がくだらない
That judgment is worthless
気に病んで下を向かないでいてね
Don't fret and look down, please
遠くから支えるくらいはいいんじゃない？
Isn't it okay to support you from afar?
欲を言えばこの手で咲かせてみせてよ
If I'm being greedy, make it bloom with these hands
病人のように心を抉らう花
A flower that gouges the heart like a sickness
枯らしたくないのさ
I don't want it to wither
光が届かずとも水をあげ続けるから
Because I'll keep watering it even if light doesn't reach
灯りが届かぬずとも水を絶やすことなく
Even if light doesn't reach, without letting the water run dry
浸し続けつづけるから
I'll keep soaking it...
いい加減に気づいて 君は素敵って
Realize soon, you're wonderful
うぬぼれてもっと大事に
Be more proud and cherish yourself more
綺麗にされた花瓶も 肥料も何も要らない
Don't need a fancy vase or fertilizer
その姿で咲き誇れ花になって
Bloom proudly in that form, become a flower
花になって
Become a flower
ほらニヒルに笑って
Look, smile cynically
その顔にぞくぞくして目が離せない
I can't take my eyes off your thrilling face
味見して君の毒は私の薬って
Taste it, your poison is my medicine
包んであげるから
I'll wrap you up
ねえ逢いたい逢いたい その笑顔に逢いたい逢いたいって言えば笑ってくれるかな
Hey, I want to see you, if I say so will you smile?
笑って
Smile
ドライフラワー
Dry Flower
多分、私じゃなくていいね
Maybe it didn't have to be me
余裕のない二人だったし
Since we were both out of room to care
気づけば喧嘩ばっかりしてさ ごめんね
Before we knew it, we were always fighting. I'm sorry.
ずっと話そうと思ってた
I'd been meaning to talk to you about it
きっと私たち合わないね
I'm sure we just weren't right for each other
二人きりしかいない部屋でさ あなたばかり話していたよね
In a room where it was just the two of us, you were always the only one talking
もしいつか何処かで会えたら 今日の事を笑ってくれるかな
If we ever meet somewhere, I wonder if you'll laugh about today
理由もちゃんと話せないけれど あなたが眠った後に泣くのは嫌
I can't explain the reasons well, but I hate crying after you fall asleep
声も顔も不器用なとこも 全部全部 嫌いじゃないの
Your voice, your face, your clumsiness—I don't hate any of it
ドライフラワーみたい 君との日々も きっときっときっときっと 色褪せる
Like a dry flower, the days with us will surely, surely fade away
声も顔も不器用なとこも 全部全部 嫌いじゃないの
Your voice, your face, your clumsiness—I don't hate any of it
ドライフラワーみたい 君との日々も きっときっときっときっと 色褪せる
Like a dry flower, the days with us will surely, surely fade away
多分君じゃなくてよかった もう流されることもないし
Maybe it's good it wasn't you, I won't be swept away anymore
私ばかりなんて言葉もなくなった
And I stopped saying things like "it's always just me"
あんなに悲しい別れでも 時間がたてば忘れてく
Even such a sad parting will be forgotten as time passes
新しいひとと並ぶ君は ちゃんと上手くやれているのかな
I wonder if you're doing well alongside someone new
もう顔も見たくないからさ 変に連絡してこないでほしい
I don't want to see your face anymore, so don't contact me strangely
都合がいいのは変わってないんだね でも無視できずまた少し返事
You haven't changed, still so convenient. But I can't ignore you and reply a bit.
声も顔も不器用なとこも 多分今も嫌いじゃないの
Your voice, your face, your clumsiness—maybe even now I don't hate them
ドライフラワーみたい 時間が経てば きっときっときっときっと 色褪せる
Like a dry flower, as time passes, it will surely, surely fade away
声も顔も不器用なとこも 全部全部 大嫌いだよ
Your voice, your face, your clumsiness—I truly despise all of it now
たぶん 私じゃなくていいよね
Maybe I'm not the one for you,
余裕のない二人だったし
Since we both had no room to spare,
気付けば喧嘩ばかりしてさ
Before we knew it, we were always fighting.
ごめんね
I'm sorry.
ずっと話そうと思ってた
I'd always intended to talk it over.
月灯りに魔物が揺れる
Monsters sway in the moonlight,
きっと私もどうかしている
I must be losing my mind too.
暗闇に色彩が浮かぶ
Colors float up in the darkness.
赤き色が胸の奥
A crimson hue deep in my chest,
ずっとあなたの名前を呼ぶ
Forever calling out your name.
好きという気持ち また香る
The feeling of love scents the air once more.
声も顔も不器用なところも
Your voice, your face, your clumsiness—
全部全部 大嫌いだよ
I hate every single bit of it.
まだ枯れない花を
Flowers that have yet to wither,
君に添えてさ
I'll offer them to you.
ずっと ずっと ずっと ずっと
Always, always, always, always,
抱えてよ
Hold onto them.
「大丈夫」とまた嘘をついた
I lied again, saying "I'm fine,"
無理してるのか声でわかるよ
I can tell by your voice you're pushing yourself.
バレてるんだよ
You've been found out.
見た目だとか 性格だって 違うあなた
Different in appearance and personality,
だけど 似てるところも 意外とあって
Yet we surprisingly share similarities too.
共鳴 すぐにしなんだ
We resonated with each other right away.
惹かれ合った 私たち
Drawn to one another,
不思議なこの絆
This mysterious bond of ours.
なんとかさ 眠れなくて
Somehow unable to sleep,
夢を語り明かそう
Let's talk about our dreams until dawn.
私がね 頑張れる理由
The reason I can keep trying—
そう 一人じゃないから
That's right, because I'm not alone.
あなたが笑えば 私もつられる
When you smile, I find myself smiling too.
隣り合わせの心 連鎖してるよ
Our side-by-side hearts are linked together.
時には 歩幅が ズレてしまうけど
Sometimes our strides might fall out of sync,
二人 呼吸 揃え
But aligning our breathing,
さあ 未来へと 進んで行こう
Come, let's step forward into the future.
どれくらいの 順位かな 周りと比べて
Wondering where we rank compared to everyone else,
果てしないトラック 先頭 追いつけるの？
Chasing the lead on an endless track—can we catch up?
なんて 弱気な日も 励まし 続けてくれた
Even on such weak-hearted days, you kept encouraging me.
あなたに いつも 感謝
I'm always grateful to you.
転んでても 立ち上がる
Even if we fall, we get back up,
夢を叶えたいんだ
Because we want to make our dreams come true.
こんなにね 打ち込めるのは
The reason we can pour ourselves into this so much
そう 同志がいるから
Is because we have each other, kindred spirits.
あなたの悩みは 私が寄り添う
I will stand close beside your worries,
心が疲れたなら 休息しよう
And if your heart grows tired, let's take a rest.
遠慮はしないで そんな仲じゃない
Don't hold back, we aren't that distant—
二人 肩を組んで
The two of us linking arms,
ほら 何度でも 乗り越えるよ
Look, we can overcome anything, time and again.
世界中が 敵になっても
Even if the whole world turns against us,
変わらず あなたの 味方
I'll always remain on your side.
右と左 友達の証だって
Right and left, tied with a ribbon of friendship,
強く固くキツく結んだ リボン
Tied strong, firm, tight, and secure.
話題のドラマも 虹の出る空も
The talked-about drama, the sky where a rainbow appears,
掴み取る 栄光も 一緒に見たい
The glory we grasp—I want to see it all together.
あなたが笑えば 私もつられる
When you smile, I find myself smiling too.
隣り合わせの心 連鎖してるよ
Our side-by-side hearts are linked together.
いずれ それぞれの道を歩いていても
Even if someday we walk our separate paths,
共に 支えになろう
Let's continue to be each other's support.
さあ 未来へと 進んで行こう
Come, let's step forward into the future.
どこにいても 二人三脚
No matter where we are, running side by side.
二人肩を組んで ほら何度でも乗り越えるよ
Arm in arm, we can overcome anything,
世界中が敵になっても
Even if the whole world turns against us,
変わらずあなたの味方
I'll always be on your side.
右と左 友達の証だよって
Right and left—a proof of friendship,
強く固くキツく縛ったリボン
A ribbon tied tightly, firmly, and strong.
話題のドラマも虹の出る空も
The trending dramas and skies with rainbows,
掴み取る栄光も一緒に見たい
The glory we grasp—I want to see it together.
あなたが笑えば私もつられる
When you smile, I can't help but smile too.
隣り合わせの心 連鎖してるよ
Our side-by-side hearts are linked in a chain.
いずれそれぞれの道を歩いても
Even if we eventually walk separate paths,
共に支えになろう さあ未来へと進んで行こう
Let's support each other. Now, let's march toward the future!
どこにいても二人三脚
No matter where we are, we walk side by side.
with you...
うえーい！できた！できた！
Yay! We did it! We did it!
２度付けと？ 忘れてたから
Double dipping? We forgot about that!
６周年、６... そっちでえ？ こっちじゃないの？
6th anniversary, 6... Wait, that way? Not this way?
韓国はこうだよ これ勉強になりました、ありがとうございます。
In Korea it's like this! I learned something new, thank you!
６がこうなんですね。おめでとう！ありがとう！おめでとう！
Ah, 6 is like this. Congratulations! Thank you! Congrats!
そうなんですよ。実はこの前、ツナのね、ライブ、誕生日ね。
That's right. Actually, recently, Tsuna's live... birthday, right?
誕生日の記念のライブにね、立たせていただいたのでね、今回。
I got to perform at her birthday anniversary live, so this time...
え、トワ様初めてなんだよね？
Wait, is this Towa-sama's first time?
そう、ホロライブのスタジオに... 決まりました！
Yes! In Hololive's studio... we decided on it!
めちゃくちゃ、いやれ、えーすごーい！ありがとうございます！
So amazing, wow, amazing! Thank you so much!
やっと吸ってきます。初めて、そう、ホロライブのスタジオで
I'm finally taking it in. For the first time, in Hololive's studio,
3Dでコラボしました！ありがとう！そしてなんと...
we did a 3D collab! Thank you! And what's more...
２年ぶりですよ。
It's been two years.
そうなんだよね。そう、この二人三脚という曲をね、やらせていただいたんですけれども。
That's right. We got to perform the song Nininsankyaku,
トワのファーストソロライブのときに、初めてやって...覚えてた？フリ。
at Towa's first solo live, we did it for the first time... Did you remember the choreography?
いやもう、完全に忘れてた。
No, I completely forgot it.
でも分かる。いろんなのやってくとね、こう忘れちゃうから。しかも２年ぶりだし。
I get it though. When you do all sorts of things, you forget. Plus it's been two years.
そう、忘れちゃったけど、でも前はさシークレットゲストだったじゃん。
Yeah, I forgot, but before, I was a secret guest, right?
で、最初なんかこうサムネで私がいる！ってなって。
And at first, seeing me in the thumbnail like I'm there! —
嬉しい！でも本当にね、あの曲、あそこで終わりじゃなくて
I was so happy! But really, that song doesn't end there,
こうやってね、またできたのがすごく嬉しいので、ありがとうございますという。
and being able to do it again like this makes me so happy, so thank you.
ということでね、なんか、ソロライブのときにコラボした後、こうやって3Dでコラボすることなかったから、今日はみなさんで無料で今お届けしているので。
So, after collaborating during the solo live, we haven't collaborated in 3D like this, so today we're delivering it for free to everyone!
無料です！はい。
It's free! Yes.
えーっと、じゃあ写真タイムするか。え？写真、改めてどういうポーズがいいですか？
Um, well, shall we do a photo time? Eh? Let's decide again, what pose is good?
指を動かしたり...ダッサイ動き。
Moving fingers around... cheesy movements.
何？今のは何？陰キャピース。
What? What was that? Introvert peace sign.
可愛い。可愛くピースやってみてよ。え？何が可愛いの？古っ。古って言われない？大丈夫？
Cute. Try doing a cute peace sign. Eh? What's cute about it? Old-fashioned. Won't people say it's old? Is that okay?
今の流行りは？今の流行り何？
What's the current trend? What's popular now?
え、これは？これは？これ私、やって、やりたいです。
Eh, what about this? What about this? I want to do this one.
おんなじやつ。ね、私もやりたいです。
The same one. Yeah, I want to do it too.
おおおお！すごーい！すごーい！ダッサい！
Ooh! Amazing! Amazing! So uncool!
喜びのダンス。え？あ、出た。
A dance of joy. Eh? Ah, there it is.
これできる。アイドル。アイドルね。アイドル。え？いぇーい！
Can we do this? Idol. Idols, right? Idol. Eh? Yay!
ありがとうございます！
Thank you very much!
いっぱい撮ってね！いっぱい撮ってね！ありがとう！
Take lots of pictures! Take lots of pictures! Thank you!
え？どう？なんだよおい！
Eh? How is it? What is that, hey!
え、ハート作るからさ、あの、グーして。
Eh, since I'm making a heart, make a fist.
トワがグーの方？うん、グーして。
Towa is the fist side? Yeah, make a fist.
こう...あ、ありがとうございます！
Like this... Ah, thank you so much!
漫画？漫画？嬉しい！え、可愛い。ステージも...
Manga? Manga? I'm so happy! Eh, cute. The stage too...
かわいい かっこいい
Cute. Cool.
ルイ姉ちゃんも可愛いじゃないですか
Lui-nee is cute too, aren't you?
え、嬉しいです
Oh, I'm so happy.
なんかすごい、なんか旗けちゃってごめんなさいね
Wow, I'm sorry for getting so hyped up.
ルイ姉ちゃんにはないものを持ってるような気がして、すごい。
It feels like you have things I don't, it's amazing.
やめてください。
Please stop.
いやでも別に何がとは言ってないんですけど、あ、そうそうでした。
I mean, I didn't say what specifically... Oh, that's right.
ということでね、今日は本当に来てくれてありがとうございます。
So, thank you so much for coming today.
え、こちらこそ、ありがとうございます。
No, thank you so much!
またね、コラボもしましょう。
Let's do another collab again.
しよう！遊ぼう！
Let's! Let's play!
遊ぼう！ということで、
Let's play! So...
以上！となわでしたー！
That's all! That was Towawa!
バイバーイ！頑張って！ありがとう！
Bye-bye! Do your best! Thank you!
群れを逸れて夢を乞うた
Straying from the pack, I begged for a dream.
それが最後になる気がしたんだ
It felt like it would be my very last.
獣は砂を一握り撒いた
The beast scattered a handful of sand.
それが最後になる気がしたんだ
It felt like it would be my very last.
不確かな夢叶えるのさ 約束の夜に
I will make that uncertain dream come true, on the promised night.
微かな風に願うのさ 静寂の朝に
I pray to the faint wind, in the quiet morning.
遠い星の少年はその腕に約束の飾り
The boy from a distant star wears a promise on his arm.
まだ旅路の途中さ 幻惑の園に
Still in the middle of our journey, in the garden of illusion.
不確かな夢叶えるのさ 約束の夜に
I will make that uncertain dream come true, on the promised night.
微かな風に願うのさ 静寂の朝に
I pray to the faint wind, in the quiet morning.
遠い星の少年はその腕に約束の飾り
The boy from a distant star wears a promise on his arm.
まだ旅路の途中さ 幻惑の園に
Still in the middle of our journey, in the garden of illusion.
遠い星の正面は
The front of a distant star...
その腕に約束の飾り
wears a promise on its arm.
まだ旅路の最中さ 幻惑の空に
Still in the middle of our journey, in the illusionary sky.
霞んで消えた
Fading and disappearing,
私の先へ
ahead of me.
それが最後に
It felt like it would be
なる気がしたんだ
my very last.
古い日の夢を
Reweaving the dreams
紡ぎ直せば
of days gone by,
それが最後に
it felt like it would be
なる気がしたんだ
my very last.
熱さを蹴り抗うのさ 約束の前に
Kicking away the heat, defying before the promise.
命綱はないのさ 逆巻く夜に
There is no lifeline, in the churning night.
まだ旅路の最中さ
Still in the middle of our journey,
惑わす空に
in the bewildering sky.
雨上がりのシャンデリア
The chandelier after the rain,
幻惑の外に
outside of illusion.
Maze of smart, sleep in deep, trip in deep in now
今宵静かに
Tonight, quietly...
今宵静けさを
Tonight, the stillness...
Pass the door, penetrate, our best before
Get triple buzz a beat
笑ったあいつもキッチュに
Even that laughing person, kitschly...
Pass the door, penetrate, our best before
What a buzz a beat, just what a buzz a beat
野良犬たちにエクスプレス
Express to the stray dogs,
桑ざのイハビ
...
永遠の意味知らぬ君に
To you, who knows not the meaning of eternity,
答えを示す時だ
it is time to show the answer.
夢幻に続く螺旋の先へ
Beyond the spiral that continues into the illusion,
(間奏)
(Instrumental Interlude)
言い訳に聞こえた理由は
The reason it sounded like an excuse
儚い未来手繰った弱さ
was the fragile weakness of chasing a fleeting future,
それを強さとはき違えている
mistaking it for strength.
憎い、憎い、醜い、醜い
Hateful, hateful, ugly, ugly.
月を隠すほどの
So black it hides the moon...
黒く、黒く澱む心
a black, stagnant heart.
君さえいなければ
If only you weren't here...
ゆらいでる、ゆらいでる、花のように意志をつなぐ
Swaying, swaying, connecting wills like flowers,
奪っていく、奪っていく
taking away, taking away,
嵐のように心を裂く
tearing hearts apart like a storm.
永遠の意味知らぬ君に答えを示す時だ
To you, who knows not the meaning of eternity, it is time to show the answer,
夢幻に続く螺旋の先に
to the spiral that continues into the illusion.
待つのは誰
Who is waiting?
生まれ落ちた運命を飲んだ
Swallowing the destiny we were born into,
背負った数の名前を覚えた
I remembered the number of names I had to bear.
爛れるほど心燃やす感情
Emotions that burn the heart until it rots away...
憎い、憎い、醜い、醜い
hateful, hateful, ugly, ugly.
世界を分かつほどの
Anger enough to tear the world apart,
怒り、怒り燃やす心
burning anger in my heart.
君さえいなければ
If only you weren't here...
ゆらいでる、ゆらいでる、花のように意志をつなぐ
Swaying, swaying, connecting wills like flowers,
奪っていく、奪っていく
taking away, taking away,
嵐のように心を裂く
tearing hearts apart like a storm.
永遠の意味知らぬ君に答えを示す時だ
To you, who knows not the meaning of eternity, it is time to show the answer,
夢幻に続く螺旋の先で
to the spiral that continues into the illusion.
鬼哭に耳を傾けた仕舞よ
Listening to the demon's cries, a dance of tragic fate,
この身に宿る万物で終わりよ
the end of all things dwelling within this body.
夢幻を他者に託した弱き人
The weak who left their illusions to others.
命の輝きは幾星霜に
The radiance of life across countless ages,
祈りの瞬きが照らす斜陽に
illuminated by the flickering prayers of the setting sun,
千夜を身に宿し解を押し付ける
embodying a thousand nights and forcing down the answers.
枯らしていく、枯らしていく、夢幻の夜に花を咲く
Withering away, withering away, making flowers bloom in the illusory night.
繋いでいく、繋いでいく、嵐に種を撒いている
Connecting, connecting, sowing seeds in the storm.
ゆらいでる、ゆらいでる、花のように意志をつなぐ
Swaying, swaying, connecting wills like flowers,
奪っていく、奪っていく
taking away, taking away,
嵐のように心を裂く
tearing hearts apart like a storm.
永遠の意味知らぬ君に答えを示す時だ
To you, who knows not the meaning of eternity, it is time to show the answer,
夢幻に続く螺旋の先で
to the spiral that continues into the illusion.
待つのは誰
Who is waiting?
以上 ゲストパートでした！
That was the guest part!
ライブなんですけれども、
This live performance...
6フェスみたいなのをちょっとイメージしてりまして、
I kind of envisioned something like a "6-Fest"...
えーとね、ダンスよりもあの、好きに動いていいのフリーの動きを多めにしたので、
Um, rather than strict choreography, I included a lot of free movement,
それぞれのゲストととわちゃんのね、個性がでてるパフォーマンスになってるんじゃないかなと思います。
so I think the performances really showcase the individuality of each guest and Towa-chan.
なので、配信とかを見直して「え、ここ癖でてるな」とか思いながらもう1回改めて見ていただけると嬉しいです。
So, I'd be happy if you could rewatch the stream and check those habits out once more.
そして、ま、この後も歌いますから、チャンネルはそのままで、ぶいーん！
And well, I'm going to sing again after this, so keep your channel right where it is!
で、プチ告知させてもらいまーす！はい！
And now, time for a little announcement! Yes!
えー、セカンドソロライブで発表いたしました、勇者パーティを追い出されたキヨビンスというアニメの主題歌「シルベ」のMVがこの後配信が終わり次第……
The MV for the theme song "Silve" from the anime announced at my 2nd solo live...
えーと、かみとわチャンネルにて上がります！
will be uploaded on Kamito-Twa Channel right after the stream ends!
めちゃくちゃいいMVになったので、ぜひぜひ見てください！
It turned out to be such an amazing MV, so please, definitely check it out!
見ないと人生を損したまではいかないかもしれないけど損するかもしれないぐらいです！はい！
If you don't watch it, you might honestly miss out on something huge! Yes!
気合を入れて作ってもらいました！はい！よろしくお願いします！
They put so much spirit into making it! Yes, thank you very much!
そして、アニメはなんと明日から放送開始！楽しみ！ぜひみてね！
And the anime starts broadcasting tomorrow! I'm so excited, be sure to watch it!
そして、MVだけではありません！ありません！
And that's not all for the MV! No, it's not!
シルベの、なんと、シングルCDが本日より予約できます！
The single CD for "Silve" is available for pre-order starting today!
なんですが、こちらの詳細は配信の最後にまとめてお伝えするので、ここもチャンネルはそのままで。
However, I'll share the details at the end of the stream, so keep the channel as is.
そしてさらに、本日はね、周年記念なので、グッズのお知らせもあります！もちろん！
And since today is our anniversary celebration, there are merch announcements too!
はい、こちらの詳細も、えー後でまたお伝えしますので、チャンネルはそのままで。
I'll share the details later, so keep the channel as is.
今日のキーワードはチャンネルはそのままで。
Today's keyword is: keep the channel as is!
え、そしてね、眠元のミニライブも今日ありますので、ぜひメンバーシップに入っていただけたら嬉しくて、チャンネルはそのままで。
And today we also have a mini-live by Nengen, so please join the membership!
どんだけ言うんだよって。
How many times are you gonna say that?!
はい、ということでありがとうございました！はい、じゃあ最後に1曲歌ってから告知しようかなと思うので、聞いてください！
Alright, thank you very much! I'll sing one last song before my announcement, so listen up!
最後の1曲、「シルベ」！
The final song, "Silve"!
watch out!! warning! warning! 寄り添い合って
watch out!! warning! warning! side by side
may god bless you 言葉の諚ね
may god bless you, it's just wordplay, isn't it
warning! warning! 彷徨いながら
warning! warning! while wandering
i will stay true to myself 'cause of you
「はじめから」みたいに 何もない世界に 理不尽と囚われる
Like "from the beginning," in a world with nothing, I am held captive by the unreasonable.
黙ってしてしまうほどの恐怖はない。
There is no fear that could make me fall silent.
使い捨てみたいに 手を離したあなたに
To you who let go of my hand as if throwing it away,
「昨日とはまるで違う」って語ったところでしようもない。
saying "it's completely different from yesterday" is pointless anyway.
変わっていく身体と 心の中で響くvoice
The changing body and the voice echoing within my heart—
間違っていなかったと ただこの空を眺めてる
I just gaze at this sky, believing I wasn't wrong.
i still 重なってくたび 思い出してしてしまうのに
I still, every time we overlap, end up remembering,
誤魔化してしてしまうのは 確かあった後悔から？
and the reason I disguise it is from the regret that was surely there?
誓ったはずなんだ さよならすらシルベにしよう
I should have sworn it—let's make even the goodbyes a guidepost.
光に触れるたび 願ってしまうように
As I wish every time I touch the light,
and still i rise!!
染まっていく 必要もない
There is no need to be dyed either.
越えられない border 揺れる意志を convert
An uncrossable border, converting the swaying will.
嘘で染めるような 日々じゃ振り返った時には heartache
Days dyed in lies bring heartache when I look back.
また夜が明ける wake up
The night breaks again, wake up,
夢の中の flavor
the flavor in my dream,
誰いなくなった 道を歩いている
walking down a road where no one is left.
今の私に 迷いすら重ねてく おとぎ話の正体
Confusion overlaps with the current me—the true form of the fairytale.
誤魔化しきれなかった 心が纏う熱を
The heat that my heart wears, which I couldn't fully disguise,
憧れが照らしてる
is illuminated by longing.
i still 重なってくたび 思い出してしてしまうのに
I still, every time we overlap, end up remembering,
誤魔化してしてしまうのは 大人になった後悔から？
and the reason I disguise it is from the regret of becoming an adult?
月明かりの夜は
On a moonlit night,
さよならすらシルベにしよう
let's turn even our goodbye into a guide.
光を繋ぐたび浮かぶ星座のように
Like constellations appearing every time we connect the light,
選んできた道のりを今を いずれ後悔してしまう時が来
the path we chose, even if a time comes when we regret it,
ても 私は まだ止まらない
I still won't stop.
夜空に浮かぶ月の光を 見上げた空に散らばる星の
The moonlight floating in the night sky,
宝石を
the starlight scattered across the sky like jewels,
道しるべにして帰る場所
making them our guide to the place we return to.
I still 重なってくたび 思い出してしてしまうのに
I still, every time they overlap, end up remembering,
誤魔化してしてしまうのは 確かにあった後悔から?
ending up brushing it aside from regrets that were surely there?
誓ったはずなんだ
We must have sworn it.
さよならすらシルベにしよう
Let's turn even our goodbye into a guide.
光に触れるたび願ってしまうように
As if wishing every time we touch the light,
And still I rise!!
染まってくことも
Even getting dyed over
どれも哀を模した true
Is all a true imitation of sorrow.
はい、ということで常闇トワ6周年記念ライブを見ていただきましてありがとうございました！
Thank you very much for watching Tokoyami Towa's 6th Anniversary Live!
ノンストップでお届けしてまいりましたが、いかがだったでしょうか？
We delivered it non-stop, but how was it?
たくさんね、タグを使って感想コメントをお待ちしております。
We are looking forward to your impressions using the tags!
ということで、この後はお知らせをさせていただきたいと思います。
With that said, I'd like to make some announcements.
まず1つめ、さっきね歌った「シルベ」を収録したシングルの発売が決定しました！イエーイ！
First, the single featuring "Silve" that I just sang has been announced! Yay!
今回のジャケット写真、グラフィ77さんに描き下ろしていただきました！
The jacket illustration for this was drawn by Graph77!
3月25日発売で、今回も全国流通での発売となります。イエーイ！
It releases on March 25th, available nationwide too! Yay!
そしてね、なんとカップリングには「Present Day」のライブバージョンが入ります！
And amazingly, the coupling includes the live version of "Present Day"!
ユアネスさん繋がりということでね、プレゼントデーはソロライブ、常闇トワセカンドライブの音源を使用した楽曲が収録されておりますので楽しみにしていてください。
Connected to youarness, it features the live sound source from my 2nd live, so look forward to it.
そして今回は完全生産限定盤と通常盤の2種をご用意しております。ということでこちらドン。
And this time, we have two editions: Limited and Regular. Here they are.
完全生産限定盤には、オリジナルTシャツが入っております。「シルベ」のジャケットイラストをつかったオリジナルTシャツとなっております。
The Limited Edition includes an original T-shirt featuring the jacket illustration.
通常盤には初回プレス限定特典として、ジャケットイラストステッカーがついてます。スマホに入れたり、ペケコンやパソコンとかに貼ってもらえたら嬉しいなと思ってます。
The Regular Edition includes a sticker. I hope you'll put it on your phone or PC!
こちら本日の21時から予約開始なんですが、
Reservations start tonight at 21:00,
なんとホロライブ公式ECではこの配信中にCDが買えるようになっているかも？ということで、楽しみに待っていてください。チェックしてね！
and you might even be able to buy it during this stream! Check it out!
そして2つめなんですが、常闇トワ活動6周年記念グッズが発売いたします！イエーイ！
And second, my 6th anniversary goods are on sale! Yay!
今回は数量限定盤もありますので、ぜひチェックしてみてください。
There's a quantity-limited edition too, so please check it out.
気になる内容は、こちらドンと、活動6周年記念フルセットこんな感じになっております。
The details are here, bam, the full set looks like this.
まず1つめはちら、「#Towavelしてね！」アクリルジオラマスタンドということでイラストは大熊まい先生に描いていただきました！
First is the acrylic diorama stand illustrated by Mai Ōkuma!
ちょっとね、大人っぽいトワちゃんと一緒にデート的なのいってもらえればなと思います。いつもねトワベルね、みんなしてくれててありがとうございます。
I hope you can enjoy a date-like feel. Thank you for always doing #Towavel!
これね、本体を取り出して、トワを取り出して一緒に写真が撮れる構図にしてるので、ぜひ一緒にねトワベルしてポストしてみてね。
You can take out the Towa figure to take photos, so please post your #Towavel!
はいでは次は、こちら！トワとお揃い！？ジャージということで、トワの通常衣装の服をイメージしたジャージになっております。
Next is the jersey, modeled after Towa's usual outfit.
これね、トワと全く一緒にするととんでもない露出度になるのでね、長めの着やすい
If it were identical it would be too revealing, so it's made long and comfortable.
はい、Mサイズにさせていただいております。
Yes, I've made it available in size M.
よかった！
I'm glad!
ちゃんと裏地もね、え、ネオンピンクみたいな形の、ネオンピンク形じゃないね、ネオンピンク色になってますから、
The lining is also neon pink—well, not neon pink shape, but neon pink in color,
本当にトワ様を、えー、になっちゃったみたいなジャージになってます。
so it really feels like you've turned into Towa-sama with this jersey.
ちょっと大きめのサイズなんで、あの、みんな着やすいのかなと思います。
Since it's a slightly larger size, I think everyone can wear it easily.
はい。
Yeah.
ということで、じゃあ最後3つ目。え、ビビハンドストラップ！
So, finally, the third item: the BiBi hand strap!
やっぱね、あの結構、あの、トワのジャージとかは結構、あの、ザ・グッズ、グッズというかさ、キャラグッズみたいな感じするんですけど、
You know, Towa's jerseys and such tend to feel like character goods,
普段使いもね、しやすいような、え、使い勝手の良いようなグッズも欲しいなと思いまして、ハンドストラップを作ってみました！
so I wanted something practical and easy for everyday use, which is why I made a hand strap!
イェーイ！
Yay!
え、カラーリングもね、すごい落ち着いていて、トワっぽい色になったんじゃないかなと思うので是非ご購入お願いいたします。
The coloring is also really calm and I think it turned out very 'Towa-like', so please consider purchasing it.
え、こちら、え、スマートフォンの画像はついておりますが、スマートフォンはついてきませんのでよろしくお願いいたします。
The smartphone image is shown here, but the smartphone itself is not included, so please be aware of that.
よろしくお願いします。
Thank you.
はい、で、こちらのねセットを、え、ご購入して下さった方には、
Yes, and for those who purchase this set,
え、笑顔のトワの、え、箔押し複製サイン入りチェキ風ブロマイドカードがついてきます。
you'll get a cheki-style bromide card with a foil-stamped replica signature of smiling Towa.
はい、で、そしてね、数量限定で直筆サイン入り、こちら直筆サインで、え、 お渡ししたいなと思っておりますので、是非どっちも手に入れてくれればなと思います。
And also, in limited quantities, with a hand-written signature—I'd love to give those out with real signatures—so I hope you can get your hands on both!
かわいい！よろしくお願いします。
So cute! Thank you very much.
ということで、えー、以上こんな感じで、え、常闇トワ6周年記念のグッズの紹介でしたー！
So, that concludes the introduction of Tokoyami Towa's 6th anniversary merchandise!
え、シルべとね、常闇トワのグッズ両方よろしくお願いいたします。
Please look forward to both 'Cilvet' and Tokoyami Towa's merchandise.
ということで今日は、見てくれてありがとー！
So thank you all for watching today!
このあとは、メン限で、ライブしますから、ぜひよろしくお願いいたしますー！
After this, I'm holding a member-only live stream, so I hope you'll join us!
いえーい！じゃあね、メンバーシップ加入と、え、グッズ購入と全部よろしくね！おけおめ！バイバーイ！
Yay! See you, and thank you for joining the membership and buying the merch! Happy New Year! Bye-bye!